gamecopyworld.eu 2019-01-21

# GameCopyWorld - Site Policies

| 

**Privacy Policy for GameCopyWorld**

**GameCopyWorld** has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our data collection and dissemination practices for this website:  **GameCopyWorld**  
  
---  
| **GameCopyWorld** uses several kinds of user data collection, these are:

  * **Data collection for statics purposes**
  * **Data collection by Ad Networks**

---  
  
**Data collection for statics purposes**  
  
**GameCopyWorld** collects the following Data collection for statics purposes:

  * **Local Data Collection**  
**GameCopyWorld** collects user data using "pixel tags", "web beacons", "clear GIFs" or similar means (collectively, "Pixel Tags") to compile aggregate statistics about usage and response rates. Pixel Tags allow us to count users who have visited certain pages of **GameCopyWorld** , to deliver advertisements for goods and services that may be of interest to you. This data is not shared with anyone else!
  * **External Data Collection**  
**GameCopyWorld** uses Google Analytics to collect user data but this is not used for advertisement purposes!

This above data collection is for **GameCopyWorld** 's internal use such as to administer our site, enhance website security, to detect broad demographic trends, to assist in providing content tailored to your interests and to otherwise enhance your experience on **GameCopyWorld**.  
  
**Data collection by Ad Networks**  
  
**GameCopyWorld** shows advertisement which come from external Ad Networks, which are not under our control. These Ad Networks collect user data. More information on specific data collection can be found here:

  * **[How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/)**

**GameCopyWorld** contains links to other sites that are not operated by us. **GameCopyWorld** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. **GameCopyWorld** provide such links only as a convenience and the inclusion of a link on **GameCopyWorld** does not imply endorsement of the linked site by **GameCopyWorld**. If you provide any personally identifiable information through any such third party website, your transaction will occur on such third party's website (and not on **GameCopyWorld** ) and the personally identifiable information you provide will be collected by and controlled by the privacy policy of that third party. We recommends that you review the privacy policy of third party websites arrived at from links on **GameCopyWorld**.  
  
**Security for GameCopyWorld**

**GameCopyWorld** has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.  
  
**General Knowledge: What are cookies?**

| Cookies are data that a web server transfers to an individual's computer for recordkeeping purposes. Cookies are an industry standard used by most websites and help facilitate users ongoing access to and use of a particular website, for example by providing information used to deliver content specific to your interests and for other purposes, such as security and other account administrative functions, and which may track personal identifying information.  
---  
Cookies do not cause damage to your computer systems or files, and only the website that transferred a particular cookie to you can read, modify or delete such cookie. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there are simple procedures in most browsers that allow you to delete existing cookies, to automatically decline cookies or to be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer of particular cookies to your computer. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. You should note, however, that declining cookies may make it difficult or impossible for you to use portions of the visiting site.  
More detailed information & video demonstration can be found @ **[http://cookies.insites.com](http://cookies.insites.com/)**. We do not operate or control this site and are not responsible for the opt-out choices available there!   
  
**GameCopyWorld** does not use, create or store cookies. We do not have access to any information about you from cookies you might receive while visiting **GameCopyWorld**.  
---  
**GameCopyWorld** however makes use of relationships with third party service providers known as Ad Networks to serve ads on **GameCopyWorld**. These Ad Networks may use cookies, which appear to be coming from **GameCopyWorld** , but in reality they are coming from the Ad Networks. Using Cookies and Pixel Tags (also known as Web Beacons), Ad Networks collect information about your visits to **GameCopyWorld** and other web sites in order to deliver advertisements that may be of particular interest to you. This process does not involve the collection of any personally identifiable information. The Ad Networks do not know your name, phone number, address, email address or any personally identifiable information. We do not share any personally identifiable information about you with these advertising networks.   
To find out more about how the networks manage the privacy of information in conjunction with delivering ads online and how to opt-out of information collection by these networks please go to: **[http://www.youradchoices.com](http://www.youradchoices.com/)** or **[http://www.networkadvertising.org](https://www.networkadvertising.org/)**. We do not operate or control these sites and are not responsible for the opt-out choices available there!   
  
**EU Data Protection Law Compliance**

**GameCopyWorld** fully complies with the European Union (EU) User Consent Policy, which requires us to obtain (EU) user consent to the storing and accessing of cookies and other information including: data collection, sharing and usage from any internal or external source, that takes place when visiting **GameCopyWorld**.
